Hello friends,
you are very welcome friends, in this
video we are going to talk
about a stock whose name is ICICI
Security Limited and
I have put a monthly time chart of the stock, I will
tell you in detail in this,
how can the stock in this video gain
momentum and where should the people who have the
stock put their stop loss
trailing, first of all
if you guys will see, then an
important area of ​​this was coming out,
why do I feel like ICICI is an opportunity, if you
guys will see, then multiple time this is a monthly
time chart and what was done in it,
multiple time this rejection
area was rejected and here it was
not even to see the momentum, like it was
broken out in it, friends, from here you got to
see a spike in
this stock, after that
if you guys will see, then the stock was
showing great intention to continue and just now if you guys will
see, then it broke down its level in the stock
and after that
what was it doing here, a  Making a reversal sign, it
again entered inside its support.
Now if you guys see, it makes
this way when the stock moves. I will
show you guys this stock,
I feel that by
making a pattern in this way, you can get to see a huge side momentum from here.
If I
talk to you guys about the entry point, then here you
guys daily, I had
shown you guys by placing a position first that you
guys have to do stock here, if you have read it, then
you guys
can keep it at a top of 400, friends. And if we
talk about the entry target, then this stock is not for me
and I am seeing returns going up to 22 seven 100. The
stock can go up to 700.
Talking about the first target, then inside it I will
tell you guys the reason that I am drawing everything
and I will tell you guys every reason
why our police
entry is going to be made inside it. As soon as I change its time frame,
you guys will see some
reversal or the other inside it
and I will tell you guys  I will also show you
how the stock can take a reversal.
Talking about the second target, the area near 700,
I will tell you again that
our entry point is going to be
friends. The current market price is hovering around 400-500.
Our first target is going to be 584.
Our second target is going to be around 700.
Around 400, right now if you guys
will see, near buy, from below if I will show you
guys by drawing a train line,
if you guys draw it online from below, then
exactly you guys will
see this stock overshooting around that. If
it comes down even a little, then I can also
make my entry again around 460
and then it can continue the upward side momentum by taking support.
Right now if I show you guys the
train line from the upper side, then it was getting
multiple times rejection, friends, this train line which was coming out,
right now if you guys look, you will
see an upward channel
inside the stock.  In this way, the
stock can be seen performing in your uploaded channel in the coming time
if
I convert the stock within the weekly time frame
and if I tell you guys here
how the candlestick is
forming, friends, if
you guys trend on the candlestick, then I
guarantee you that 90% of the time
you will be correct, the way the
candlestick is forming, it is completely 2G
and if you guys
see any 2G forming on the supports, or multiple
times, then the possibility of
reversal increases a lot from there, in this way the
acceleration price can continue the momentum on its own,
I provide you guys with similar live wireless on my channel
daily, you
guys can go and watch and one more thing,
my channel friends, if you guys have any
doubt, then you guys can also ask me in the comments,
I will
reply to you immediately and through shorts, you
guys will get Nifty Bank in the early morning.
Nifty provides a lot of overview.
For more content like this live education,
subscribe to the channel
vidyalali Jai Hind in the video.